Finding Aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) Audiovisual Materials
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Audio Materials
  - Audio Reel-to-Reel News Briefs, 1975-1994
    - 9 August 1983-15 September 1983, Matthaei docent program, Saul Hymans updating Economic outlook conference forecast, Richard Curtin on consumer sentiment, John Savage of Michigan Commerce Department at ISDOS Inc., luncheon, James Jackson, Ronald Brown on black voters, Jesse Jackson, Summer commencement (missing), Eric Becher on fall band practices beginning, Regents meetings. (Box 5)
    - 16 September 1983-12 October 1983, Regents meeting, B.E. Frye at Faculty Senate Assembly, marital therapists (promo for upcoming Heath Night Out), Announcement of funding of Geriatric Education Center, groundbreaking for Fine Arts Building addition, Michael Traugott at University Press Club of Michigan, State of University address, Obstetrician-gynecologist William Rayburn on Every Womans Pharmacy: A Guide to Safe Drug Use, Doug Herland on Rowing on the Rover Festival. (Box 5)
    - 13 October 1983-26 October 1983, Campaign for Michigan (Cosovich and Ford), Campaign for Michigan, Liz Ausman on Homecoming week events, Becher on music range of Marching band, Regents, Haig, Wagenaar, Maurer, Nordley at Campus Meet the Press. (Box 5)
    - 28 October 1983-17 November 1983, James Kulik on results of test coaching on college admissions tests scores, Beatrice Kalisch on nurse stereotypes, Pete Pellerito on United Way success among UM givers, Lawrence Crocket on computerized statewide info network to help in technology transfer, Gardner Ackley on Leviathan theory of government, Richard Curtin on consumer sentiment, Saul Hymans Joan Cracy on Economic outlook Conference forecasts. (Box 5)
    - 22 November 1983-2 January 1984, Susumu Nagara on The Day After compared to Hiroshima, Groundbreaking for Medical Research Building, Engineering College/Apple/Apollo news conference., Barbara Richardson on her research into economic effects of putting air bags in all autos, Richard Lapman on cold weather heart care, Summer Festival news conference, Regents meetings, Winter commencement (Mackey), David Rea, Robert Own on hydrothermal activity. (Box 5)
    - 16 March 1984-3 April 1984, Dr. Douglas Behrendt on heart transplant, Cronkite at commencement, Steven Emede on 1-M-B Nuclear decay experiment, Nancy Reame on tampons, Regents meetings, Pollack Sederbury at Faculty Senate Assembly, Norman Mailer at Hopwood awards, Richard Lampman on heart disease to promote first in series of workshops, David Brophy on State Capital, Frank Rhodes at honors convocation, Russian migrs news conference and panel. (Box 5)
    - 16 February 1984-20 March 1984, US/Japan Auto Conference, Michael Driggs, Owen Bieber, H.A. Poling, Gerald Greenwald, Roach, Power at Faculty Senate Assembly, Regents meetings, Prof. Mc Sparren on St. Patricks Day, Hymans updates Conference on the Economic Outlook forecast, Regents meeting. (Box 5)
    - News Conference, 10 January 1984-15 February 1984, Ann Arbor Technology Park news conference announcing state retirement fund loan, Regents meetings, Charles Bolden Jr. news conference, William Martel on new UM Hospitals magnetic resonance imaging unit, Robert Cole on US/Japan Auto Study, Power Scholar news conference, Lloyd Johnston on High School student drug use, Curtin on consumer sentiment, Bernstein news conference at Vienna Philharmonic rehearsal. (Box 5)
    - 22 March 1990-20 September 1990, Regents meetings, Edward Heaths lecture, Regents meetings, Rackham Graduate Exercises: Frank Rhodes, Regents Meetings: 22 March-20 September. (Box 5)
    - 18 October 1990-20 December 1990, Regents meeting summaries, 2nd-6th day reports from World Solar Challenge, Winter Commencement: Robert Nederlander, Regents meetings. (Box 5)
    - 15 November 1990, Sit-in Ends, Saul Hymans on National Economy, Regents summary. (Box 5)
    - 21 November 1991, Saul Hymans summary of National economic outlook. (Box 5)
    - 13 April 1993-10 March 1994, Lloyd Johnston on substance abuse among youth, young adults, Spring Commencement: Hillary Rodham Clinton, Prof. Jeffrey Chamberlain on Duchene Muscular Dystrophy, Cancer Center/ Geriatric Center groundbreaking, Harold Poling at School of Business Administration, Regents meeting summary, Prof. Kenneth Warner on economic impact of reduced tobacco sales, Regents meetings. (Box 5)
    - Interviews shortly before and during the 1980 reunion of UM Symphony Band members who toured the Soviet Union in 1961., 7-inch; 4 audiotapes (reel-to-reel; Interviews include William Revelli, Donald Sinta, George Cavendish and Fred Moncrieff. Fred was director of the UM News Service in 1961 and traveled with the band. (Box 5)
- Video Materials
  The Video Materials series consists of the following subseries: Affirmative Action and Campus Diversity; Arts and Cultural Events; the University of Michigan Commencement and Graduate Exercises; Information Technology Division; Institutional Messages and Promotions; International Issues and Foreign Studies Lectures; Lectures and Symposia; Martin Luther King Jr. Memorial Keynote; Medical and Health Sciences News Clips and Promotions; Michigan Replays; Miscellaneous News and Media Coverage; The Royal Shakespeare Company Residency; Saturday Morning Physics Lectures; Science Lectures; Statements and Media Events on University Presidents; University Orientation Video; University of Michigan Solar Car; and Wolverine Sports Magazine.
  - Affirmative Action and Campus Diversity, 1995-2003
    The Affirmative Action and Campus Diversity subseries includes media coverage from the major Supreme Court cases in the late 1990s and early 2000s related to affirmative action admissions practices at the University of Michigan, as well as University responses to the Court decisions and media produced by the University addressing how it intends to address campus diversity. The subseries includes 14 VHS tapes, 3 DVCam tapes, and 2 DVD video discs.
    - ABC World News Tonight, American Agenda, Affirmative Action and College Admissions, July 20, 1995, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - [Affirmative Action] Court Decision March 27, Court Decision March 28, MSNBC, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - University of Michigan Law School Campus Diversity B-Roll, June 21, 1999, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Affirmative Action: Where Do We Stand? September 25, 1999, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - ABC News Special, Hopkins 24/7 Show #3 "ZACH" September 06, 2000, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Towards an Inclusive University: Stories from the History of Diversity at the University of Michigan 1999, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - "60 Minutes" University of Michigan July 8, 2001, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - "60 Minutes" University of Michigan May 26, 2002, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Detroit Economic Club Luncheon, Dr. Mary Sue Coleman presents "After the Storm: the Next Michigan", January 21, 2003, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Campus Diversity, Student Voices September 2002-April 2003, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Affirmative Action on Trial, August 26, 2003, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Towards an Inclusive University: A Partial History of Diversity of UM;[Undated], VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - Defending Affirmative Action, Richard Lempert, April 10, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 13)
    - Affirmative Action; UM Admissions Lawsuits: An Update; September 18, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 13)
    - UM Admissions Lawsuits: An Update; September 18, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 13)
    - Supreme Court Affirmative Action coverage; approximately 7 minutes, June 23-24, 2003, DVD Video (Box 13)
    - Supreme Court Affirmative Action coverage, edited; 4:50, June 23-24, 2003, DVD Video (Box 13)
    - UM on Supreme Court Decision on Affirmative Action, CBS Evening News, ABC World News Tonight, "Today" show on NBC, June 24, 2003, VHS Tape (Box 13)
    - President Mary Sue Coleman "Stakeout" Outside Huetwell Visitors Center, March 20, 2003, VHS Tape
  - Arts and Cultural Events at the University of Michigan, 2002-2004
    The Arts and Cultural Events subseries consists of 17 DVCam tapes dated between 2002 and 2004. The content of these tapes centers on theater events at the University and the year-long "Projecting Petersburg" event that showcased the arts and cultural achievements of the Russian city of St. Petersburg. Other events include a "Sousa Spectacular Event", film shorts from the Ann Arbor Film Festival, and musical and arts performances at the University of Michigan. Not included in this subseries is the Royal Shakespeare Company Residencies of 2001, 2002, and 2003, which are arranged in their own subseries further in this collection.
    - "My Life in the Theater" 2002 Vivian R. Shaw Lecture, Wendy Wasserstein, September 18, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Wendy Wasserstein, September 18, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Charlotte Salomon's "Leben Oder Theater" Girselda Pollock, January 22, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Sousa Spectacular October 20, 2002 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Projecting Petersburg: "Architecture Urban Legacy," March 8, 2003 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Projecting Petersburg: Kirov-Mariinsky "Culture / Urban Catalyst", March 8, 2003 UMTV 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Literary Petersburg: "From Pushkin to Brodsky," October 2, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - "St. Petersburg: City as History," William Rosenberg, October 9, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - The Gershwin Showcase, October 24, 2003 UM 22 Edit, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - "Nicholas I & The Hermitage: Builder, Patron, & Tastemaker", Anne Odom, October 26, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Ache! Drums and Women, November 11, 2003, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Fire & Blood for Violin & Orchestra, Professor Michael Daugherty, March 9, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - Bolcom and Blake, "Artists at Work" April 6, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - AAFF Shorts, Nine for TV, Art and Design [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - In The Music Shop, [Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - [In The Music Shop, Undated], DVCam Tape (Box 7)
    - The Band Director, [Undated], DVCam Tape
  - The University of Michigan Commencements and Graduate Exercises, 1987-2011
    The Commencement and Graduate Exercises subseries consists of 30 tapes of mixed video formats: U-matic, DVCam and VHS tape. Commencement speeches include the 1987 Mike Wallace address, George H.W. Bush in 1991, Hillary Rodham Clinton in 1993, and Rick Snyder in 2011. Some of these tapes were given to regional and Detroit TV stations for rebroadcast on local news networks but do not represent a complete selection of the commencement and graduate exercises collected by the University. Other tapes (the VHS in particular) are home video versions sold to students, alumni, and their family.
    - Commencement: Spring 1987, Regional TV coverage of UM spring commencement at which Mike Wallace was main speaker: WXYZ-TV, WDIV-TV, Detroit, May 2, 1987, U-Matic Tape (Box 10)
    - LS& A Commencement, 1990, U-Matic Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Spring 1991, Television coverage of President George H.W. Bush at UM spring commencement: WJBK-TV, WDIV-TV, WXYZ-TV, WKBD-TV, Detroit; "CBS Evening News"; "NBC Nightly News"; "ABC World News Saturday." May 4, 1991, U-Matic Tape (Box 10)
    - Hail to the Victors, Hail to the Chief: Highlights from the 1991, Spring Commencement, 1991, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - LS&A Commencement, Spring 1992, U-Matic Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Spring 1993, Regional Television coverage of Hillary Rodham Clinton's University Graduation Ceremony speaking: WDIV-TV, WJBK-TV, WXYZ-TV, May 1, 1993, U-Matic Tape (Box 10)
    - First of May with the First Lady, University of Michigan Spring Commencement, May 1, 1993, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement, April 29, 1995, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement, Speaker Johnetta Cole, May 4, 1996, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement, May 3, 1997, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement, May 2, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Winter Commencement December 20, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Winter Commencement, December 19, 1999, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - "Past is Prologue" University of Michigan Winter Commencement, Speaker: Ken Burns, December 14, 1997, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - New Student Convocation: September 1999, DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement 1999, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement 2000, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement 2001, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Spring Commencement 2002, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Winter Commencement 2000, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Winter Commencement 2001, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - University of Michigan Winter Commencement 2002, VHS Tape (Box 10)
    - Graduate Exercises: Spring 2002, Hill Auditorium, April 26, 2002, DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Winter 2003 December 13, 2003 (UM 22 Edit), DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Spring 2004,May 1, 2004 (UM 22 Edit), DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Winter 2004, December 19, 2004, DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Spring 2005, April 30, 2005 (Michigan TV 2), DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Winter 2005, December 18, 2005, DVCam Tape (Box 10)
      ([Tape inside box says Michigan Replay 2003 Tape 2])
    - Commencement: Winter 2005, December 18, 2005 Michigan Channel, DVCam Tape (Box 10)
    - Commencement: Spring 2011, Rick Snyder, 2011, DVCam Tape
  - Information Technology Division, 1989-1999
    The Information Technology Division subseries consists of 102 video tapes of mixed formats, including: U-Matic, Betacam Tape, VHS tape, and DVCam tape. The content of these materials was produced by the University of Michigan's Information Technology Division between 1989 and 1999 and features interviews with ITD members, services offered by ITD, and training material for ITD employees. Researchers will also find materials relevant to Y2K preparedness, public announcements of contracts between the University and computer contractors, and lectures and symposia on the subject of University computing.
    - The Electronic Classroom at the University of Michigan, 1987, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - UM Educom '89 Panel Discussion, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - "Partners in the Future", the UM Information Technology Division, 1989, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - Video Segments for All Staff Meeting ITD, November 1989, U-Matic Tape (Box 20)
    - An Introduction to Computer Resources at the University of Michigan, Susan P. Harris, BS, Med, 1991, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - Computing at the University of Michigan, Information Technology Division, 1995, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - CITI; Kitty Bridges Interview, March 14, 1995, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - CITI; Kitty Bridges/Laura Patterson Interviews, March 14-17, 1995, VHS Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 1; April 19, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 2; April 19, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 3, B-Roll Gabe/Bryant, April 24, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 4; April 11, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 5; April 11, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 6, May 2, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 7, April 6, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 8, April 6, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 9, March 27, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 10, March 27, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Tape 11, March 27, 1995, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - Master -- Computing at the University of Michigan, Judy Dean, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - ITD Customers #3, 1996, U-Matic Tape (Box 20)
    - The Many Faces of ITD, 1996, U-Matic Tape (Box 20)
    - Introducing ITD Building Count, 1996, U-Matic Tape (Box 20)
    - Introducing ITD March 1996, February 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - Next Step in Customer Service Rough Footage, Reel 1, March 1, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - Next Step in Customer Service Rough Footage, Reel 2, March 1, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - Next Step in Customer Service Rough Footage, Reel 3, March 6, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - Next Step in Customer Service Rough Footage, Reel 4, March 6, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 20)
    - Climbing the Walls, (ITD-Kinesiology), October 1996, U-Matic Tape (Box 20)
    - VR Conference, October 4, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - VR Conference, October 4, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - VR Symposium, October 6, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - Customer Focus Roundtable with Jose-Marie Griffiths, 1 of 2, December 1996, U-Matic Tape (Box 21)
    - Customer Focus Roundtable with Jose-Marie Griffiths, 2 of 2, December 1996, U-Matic Tape (Box 21)
    - Information Technology Division Customer Focus Group, Time-Out Retreat Pre-Meeting Video, December 2, 1996, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - Center for Highly Interactive Computing in Education at UM "7th Graders Using Hi-CE's Technologies in Science Inquiry", 1997, VHS Tape (Box 21)
    - M-Pathways, January 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 21)
    - Jose-Marie Griffiths, Customer Facing Q&A, May 27, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - Edit Master "Customer Facing" May 28, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 21)
    - Jose-Marie Griffiths Knowledge Communities/IBM Review, West Hall, June 17, 1997, VHS Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Eric Rabkin Interview, Tape 1, June 24, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Eric Rabkin Interview, Tape 2, June 24, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Eric Rabkin and Gary Olson Interview, Tape 3, June 24, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Tom Finholt Interview, Tape 4, June 24, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Tom Finholt Judy Olson Interview, Tape 5, June 24, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Judy Olson Interview, Tape 6, June 24, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 21)
    - ITD Perry Samson (Weather Underground) Interview, Tape 7, June 26, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Perry Samson (Weather Underground) Interview, Tape 8, June 26, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Perry Samson (Weather Underground) Interview, Tape 9, June 26, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Perry Samson June 26, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - Rabkin--Perry Samson Roll, ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, June 26, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Tim Killeen June 30, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Knowledge Communities Tim Killeen Interview Tape 10, June 30, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Knowledge Communities Tim Killeen Interview Tape 11, June 30, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Tim Killeen June 30, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - Mary Simoni, ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Tape 1 of 3 July 1, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - Mary Simoni, ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Tape 2 of 3 July 1, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - Mary Simoni, ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Tape 3 of 3 July 1, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview with Mary Simoni, Tape 12, July 1, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview with Mary Simoni, Tape 13, July 1, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Richard Rockwell July 3, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Richard Rockwell Interview, Tape 15, July 3, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Richard Rockwell Interview, Tape 16, July 3, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD David Featherman Interview, Tape 17, July 3, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, David Featherman July 3, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Nancy Butler Songer Interview, Tape 18, July 3, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Nancy Butler Songer Interview, Tape 19, July 3, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Angell Hall B-Roll July 3, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - Netscape B-Roll, ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Tape 1 of 2; July 11, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Interview/Knowledge Communities Video, Nancy Butler-Songer, July 11, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD #21, Performance Ensemble B-Roll, July 11, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - ITD Knowledge Community Collaboratories, July 22, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - University of Michigan, Information Technology, Knowledge Community Collaboratories, July 22, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 22)
    - M-Quality Expo 1997 Build the Bridge as You Walk on It, October 16, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - M-Quality Expo 1997 Welcome Deep Change: Discovering the Leader Within, October 16, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - M-Quality Expo 1997 Teamwork: A Key to Success, October 16, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - M-Quality Expo 1997 Build the Bridge as You Walk on It, October 17, 1997, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Knowledge Communities: Technology, Tradition, & Transformation in Higher Education, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 23)
    - Knowledge Communities, May 28, 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Knowledge Communities, May 28, 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Jose-Marie Griffiths V/O M. Berger, July 16, 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Ameritech Learning Initiative, September 19, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 23)
    - UM /IBM Announcement, September 21, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 23)
    - Jose-Marie Griffiths Shoot, Geer School House, September 30, 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Jose-Marie Griffiths Geer School House, September 30, 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Knowledge Communities, Technology, Tradition, and Transformation in Higher education, November 1998, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - The InfoTech Channels 26/27, Cable Television Other, Video Text, November 18, 1998, VHS Tape (Box 23)
    - Y2K Preparedness Drill, December 7, 1999 Tape 1 of 2, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Y2K Preparedness Drill, December 7, 1999 Tape 2 of 2, Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - CITI; MVS Distributed Campus, [Undated], VHS Tape (Box 23)
    - Ameritech Signing: Nancy Cantor, Bob Cooper; IBM Signing, Lee Bollinger, Sean Rush [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 23)
    - Technology: Possibilities in the Hands of the People, Jose-Marie Griffiths, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Knowledge Communities, [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 23)
    - Simoni, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Rabkin, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Early Knowledge Communities Rough Cuts, Ameritech IBM Signings, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Upper Atmosphere Research Collaboratory, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 23)
    - Simon #2 B-Roll, [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 23)
    - Workplace 2000 with Maureen Burns, June 4, 1997, U-Matic Tape (Box 23)
    - Future of Computing FOC 19, [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 23)
    - Future of Computing FOC 20, [Undated], U-Matic Tape (Box 23)
    - Future of Computing FOC 21, [Undated], U-Matic Tape
  - Institutional Messages and Promotions, 1979-2003
    The Institutional Messages and Promotions subseries consists of 99 tapes of mixed video formats: U-matic, DVCam, Betacam, and VHS Tape, dated from 1970 to 2003. Included in this subseries are video recordings of institutional messages about the University played during commercial breaks for sporting events, promotional materials about activities going on at the University, marching band performances, and materials and media releases prepared by the News and Information Service about scholarly activity going on at the University.
    - Ann Arbor campus scenes, [between 1970 and 1980], DVCam Tape (Box 16)
    - Ann Arbor campus scenes, [between 1980 and 1990], DVCam Tape (Box 16)
    - Ann Arbor campus scenes, [between 1980 and 1990], U-Matic Tape (Box 16)
    - Ann Arbor campus scenes, [Undated], Betacam Tape (Box 16)